It's guys.
The soldier's rescue.
Chevas.
Let's go,
Juninho.
Let me put on the double helmet,
eh, rascal,
today is forty-six,
so he leaves.
88.
I bought the piece.
I'm going out on the sink now.
See if you have a rope to borrow.
He's called to pull the car,
pull a Chevette,
man,
he's got a rope to borrow.
No, it's not going there.
He talks to Rafael,
then he arrives at Rafael,
talks to Rogério,
then he talks to Rogério,
no,
but he talks to tizil tizil has a string,
he goes to tizil,
he talks to there,
he talks to where I can't borrow .
Not that string.
Who belongs to Fernando?
Then Fernando isn't enough,
you're the little uncle.
Beauty.
The sergeant spoke to you.
Yeah,
the won't roll today.
There's how they help me rescue the chevas.
You're missing a frontman here today.
The guy who could strengthen me.
Oh,
it's full of cars in here,
oh,
the shed there didn't rent.
I asked to see if he would let me rehearse my talk.
I wrote something down to speak in my new talk,
but it's all scattered like this,
you know,
I need to organize the order.
Please stop.
Yesterday they called me crazy and today they pay to listen to my ideas.
Po,
this one is strong.
I think this EU will use,
right?
If people like your presence,
they will take care of your absence.
Is it on?
It's all about telling history.
Are those married or not?
Cê conquered his wife,
brother, and then,
when you go to sleep,
you will tell a little story to your daughter,
man,
that same story that you tell with this enthusiasm is
the story that you need to tell for you to make your sale .
Are you on today?
I'm going to tell you a secret,
brother.
It's much more fun.
Now you need to organize these ideas.
I don't know how big your dream is.
You know, dude,
when you're really determined to achieve it,
man,
I've got dark circles under my eyes from sleepless nights,
but I'm faithful to my dream.
Man,
I'm there fighting and battling for him.
Are you connected sooner or later?
I'll reap the rewards if you just stand there waiting.
Comparing your life to the other person,
because he doesn't like me,
because I can't sell.
The biggest secret is not trying to convince others,
but convincing yourself.
Thank you,
no need,
you can stand,
you can't sit,
bro,
thank you.
Hopefully it goes well,
huh?
We're in this together.